<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="women_safety">Women Safety</string>
    <string name="threat">Tips To Escape From Threat</string>

    <string name="tips">1. What should a woman do if she finds herself alone
        in the company of a stranger male as she prepares to
        enter a lift in a High Rise apartment late at night ....???\n\n

Experts Say : Enter the lift......if you need to reach the 13th floor,press all the buttons
        up to your destination. No one will dare attack you in a lift that stops on every floor.\n\n

        2. What to do if a stranger tries to attack you when you when you are alone in your in your house,run into the kitchen.\n\n

Experts Say : You alone know where the chilli powder and turmeric are kept.
        And where the knives and plates are. All these can be turned into deadly weapons.
        If nothing else, start throwing plates and utensils all over. Let them break.
        Scream...Remember that noise is the greatest enemy of a molester. He does not want to be caught.\n\n

        3. Taking an Auto or Taxi at night.\n\n

Experts Say : Before getting into an auto at night, note down its registration number.
        Then use the mobile to call your family or friend and pass on the details to them
        in the language the driver understands. Even if no one answers your call, pretend
        you are in a conversation. The driver now knows someone has his details and he will
        be in serious trouble if anything goes wrong. He is now bound to take you home safe
        and sound. A potential attacker is now de facto protector.\n\n


        4. What if the driver turns into a street he is not supposed too and you feel you are entering a danger zone...\n\n

Experts Say :  Use the handle of your purse or your stole (dupatta) to wrap around his
        neck and pull him back. Within seconds, he will feel chocked and helpless.
        In case you dont have a purse or stole just pull him back by his collar.
        The top button of his shirt would then do the same trick.\n\n

        5. If you are stalked at night...

Expert Say : Enter a shop or a house and explain your predicament. If it is night
        and shops are not open, go inside an ATM box. ATM centres always have
        close circuit television.Fearing
       identification, no one will dare attack you.\n\n

After all, being mentally alert is the greatest weapon you can ever have.</string>

    <string name="tips_regarding_women_safety">Tips Regarding Women Safety</string>
    <string name="paragraph">1. Woman must have all the emergency numbers with them and WhatsApp also if possible so that they can immediately tell to their family member and police.\n\n
2. Hold your bag as tightly as you can when you are taking public transport. You can use it to hit your predator.\n\n
3. When you are walking on a road,  keep your mobile phone handy but avoid using it. Being on the phone makes you less alert.\n\n
4. When you are travelling in an auto alone, make sure you share the auto number with someone in your family even if its during the day.\n\n
5. Similarly, if you have booked a cab, always share your coordinates with someone.\n\n
6. When in office, avoid going to isolated areas with no CCTV cameras.\n\n
7. If you have parked your car, always look underneath, especially at night or at less-crowded area.\n\n
Very Important\n\n
8. Whenever you are posting anything on social media, make sure you dont do it in real-time. Because if you do, you are telling people on your social media about your whereabouts. Delay those posts by say, 20-30 minutes.\n\n
9. Always ensure you are not posting anything  on your social media with your address or phone number on it.\n\n
10. Whenever you are giving out order for delivery at a grocery store, make sure you whisper your address or write it down somewhere and give it to the shopkeeper. Never announce it.\n\n
11. Whenever you are getting your phone recharged, if its at a store, dont loudly speak up your phone number.\n\n
12. Always pour your own drinks at parties and dont ever take drinks from complete strangers or even friends. If you have left your drink unattended for even a few minutes, leave it and get a fresh drink. It may have been spiked when you weren not looking.\n\n
13. If you feel someone is stalking you, try to find a crowded place and call someone for help.\n\n
14. Self defence techniques are the first and foremost thing to which end and every woman must be aware of and get proper self-defence training for their safety. They must be aware of some effective defences techniques such as kicks to groin, blocking punches, etc.\n\n
15. Generally most of the women are gifted with sixth sense which they must use whenever they become in some problem. They should  at once avoid any situation which they feel bad for them.\n\n
16. Escape and run is also a good way to reduce some risks of women whenever they become in problem. They should never go with any unknown person alone at some unknown places.\n\n
17. Women must understand and feel their physical power and use accordingly. They never feel themselves weak than men and take some self defence training.\n\n
18. They should be careful while communicating with someone on internet in the cyberspace.\n\n
19. Pepper spray can also be proved as a useful self-defence tool however it has a drawback that some people cannot be harmed through it even after full-face spray. it may not stop the attacker so women should not dpend on it completely and use other techniques also.\n\n
20. Women should be very conscious while driving the car and going to any trip. They must lock all the doors of car while traveling with own or private car.</string>
    <string name="laws">The Indian Penal Code, 1860, lays down the provisions to penalise the culprit for the heinous offences against women. Various sections under IPC specifically deals with such crimes.</string>
    <string name="murder">Murder,Dowry death,Abetment Of Suicide,etc. (Sections 302,304B and 306)</string>
    <string name="cruelity">Cruelty by husband or his relatives (Section 498A)</string>
    <string name="outraging">Outraging the modesty of women (Section 354)</string>
    <string name="sexual">Sexual harassment (Section 354A)</string>
    <string name="assault">Assault on women with intent to dirobe a woman (Sections 354B)</string>
    <string name="voyeurism">Voyeurism (Section 354C)</string>
    <string name="stalking">Stalking (Section 354C)</string>
    <string name="word">Word, gesture or act intended to insult the modesty of a woman (Section 509)</string>
    <string name="kidnapping">Kidnapping and abduction for different purposes (Sections 363-373)</string>
    <string name="rape">Rape (Section 375,376,376A,376B,376C,376D and 376E)</string>
    <string name="acid">Acid Attack (Section 326A and 326B)</string>
    <string name="Acid_Attack">Acid Attack (Sections 326A and 326B)</string>
    <string name="acid_law">The Criminal Law ( Amendment ) Act, 2013 incorporated Section 326A and 326B with an itend to make specific provision for punishment in the case of acid attack.\n\n
Section 326A focuses on voluntarily causing grievous hurt by using acid. In the view of this section, whoseever  causes permanent or partial damage or burns, disfigures or disbles any part of the body of a person or causes grievous hurt by throwing or adminstering acid with an intention to cause such imprisonment of at least ten years which may extend to life imprisonment with fine.\n\n
Section 326B has more legislative focus on the act of throwing or attempting to throw acid with the intention of causing grievous hurt. The punishment under this section is imprisonment of not less than five years with fine which may extend upto seven years.\n\n
Essential ingredients of Acid Attack\n
The following are the requisites of an acid attack-\n\n
1. Permanent/partial damage /deformity/burn/idfigure/disable any part of the body of any person; or\n\n
2. Grievous hurt by throwing acid; or\n\n
3. By using any other means;\n\n
4.  There must be an intention to cause injury or hurt. </string>
    <string name="rape_law">Rape (Section 375, 376, 376A, 376B, 376C, 376D and 376E)</string>
    <string name="rape_laws">Section 375, IPC defines rape. In simple terms, the offence of rape is the ravishment of a women, without her consent, by force, fraud or fear. In other words , it is the carnal knowledge ( penetration of any of the slightest degree of the male orrgan of reproduction ) of any woman by force against her will. It is an obnoxious act of highest degree which violates the right to privacy and sanctity of a female. Apart from being a dehumanising and perverted act, it is also an unlawful interference in the personal life of a woman which is an intense blow on the honour, dignity, reputation and self-esteem of a woman. This outrageous crime not only cause physical injury to the victim but also humiliates, degrades and leaves a scar on the most precious jewel of a woman i.e. her character and dignity.\n\n
Essential Ingredients Of Rape\n\n
        Section 375 has the following two essential ingredient-\n\n
1. Actus Reus: There must be sexual intercourse, as understood in terms of the provisions of Section 375 (a) to (d), with a woman by a man.\n\n
2. Mens Rea: The sexual intercourse must be under any of the circumstances as given under Section 375.\n\n
 Punishment for Rape (Section 376)\n\n
1.Section 376 provides punishment for committing the heinous crime of rape. This section is divided into two sub-sections.\n\n
2.Section 376(1) provides a minimum sentence of seven years of imprisonment that may extend to life imprisonment and fine.\n\n
3. Section 376(2) provides punishment not less than ten years of imprisonment but may extend to imprisonment for life or death or fine.\n\n
  Gang Rape ( Section 376D )\n
Section 376D lays down the punishment for gang rape. Where a woman is raped by more than one person acting in furtherance of a common intention, each of them shall be liable for the offence of rape and shall be punished with rigorous imprisonment for not less thantwenty years which may extend to lifetime imprisonment and fine.</string>
    <string name="kidnapping_law">Kidnapping And Abduction For Different Purposes (Sections 363-373)</string>
    <string name="para">Section 363 in the Indian Penal Code punishment for kidnapping. - Whoever kidnaps any person from India or from lawful guardianship shall be punished imprisonment of either description for a term which may extend to seven years, and shall also be liable to fine\n\n
Section 373 in the Indian Penal Code buying minor of purposes of prostitution, etc.\n
-Whoever buys, hires or otherwise obtains possession of any\n\n
1. [person under the age if eighteen years wuth intent that such person shall at any age beemployed or used for the purpose of prostitution or illicit intercourse with any person or for any unlawful and immoral purpose, of knowing it to be likely that such person will at any age be] employed or used for any purpose, shall be punished imprisonment of either desciption for a term which may extend to ten years, and shall also be liable to fine.\n\n
2. [Explanation 1. - Any prostitute or any person keeping or managing a brothel, who buys, hires or otherwise obtains possession of a female under the age of 18 year shall, until the contrary is proved, be presumed to have obtained possession of such female with the intent that she shall be used for the purpose of prostitution.</string>
    <string name="abetment">Dowry death and bride burning are sinful act which are still privailing in the Indian society. It is a symptom of a special social illeness and are unfortunate developments of our society. For this serious matter, the special provision was inserted under IPC through Section 304B which deals with dowry deaths.\n\n
Section 304B(1) defines dowry death where clause (2) lays down its punishment  which is not less than seven years and may extend to life imprisonment.\n\n
Essential ingredients of Dowry Death\n\n
The following ingredients of the offence need to be established-\n\n
1. The death of a women must be caused by burns or bodily injury or otherwise then under normal circumstances.\n\n
2. Such death must occur within the period of seven years of marriage.\n\n
3. The woman must have been subjected to cruelity by her husband or any other relative of her husband.\n\n
4. Such cruelity must be in connection with demand of dowry.\n\n
5. Such cruelity must be shown out soon before her death.</string>
    <string name="abetment_law">Murder, Dowry death, Abetment of suicide, etc. (Sections 302, 304B and 306 )</string>
    <string name="cruelity_law">Cruelity by husband Or his relatives (Section 498A )</string>
    <string name="cruel">A separate chapter of IPC deals with the issues of cruelity by a husband of or his relatives under Section 498A,IPC.  the objective behind the introduction of this provision was to punish the husband and his relative who torture, ill-treat and harass a woman with the view to force her or any other person related to her to meet any unlawful demands.\n\n
This Section has given a new dimension to the concept of cruelity which is the essence of this Section, for the purpose of matrimonial relief. Not every type of cruelity will attract Section 498A. It has been mentioned under the Section that what kind of cruelity is included hereby.\n\n
The punishment for this offence is imprisonment for a term which may extend to three years with fine.\n\n
Essential ingredients\n\n
To constitute an offence under Section 498A, the following are the neccessary conditions-\n\n
1. The victim must be a married woman/widow.\n\n
2. She has been subjected to cruelity by her husband or his relatives.\n\n
3. Such cruelity consisted of either-\n\n
-> Harassment of a women with a view to coerce her meeting a demand of dowry, or\n\n
->A wilful conduct by the husband or his relatives of such a nature as is likely to lead the lady to commit suicide or to cause grave injury to her life, limb or health\n\n
That such injury inflicted either physically or mentally.
</string>
    <string name="outraging_the_modesty_of_women_section_354">Outraging the modesty of women ( Section 354 )</string>
    <string name="outraging_laws">Section 354, IPC deals with the offence of molestation i.e. assault to women with intent to outrage her modesty. This Section aims to protect women against any sort of incident or filthy behaviour by others which is derogatory to her modesty. This offence is not just against the individual but also against the society and public morality. Thereore, if any person uses criminal fore upon awomen with an intention to outrage the modest of a women. He is deemed to be punished with an imprisonment of not less than one year which may extend upto five year with fine.\n\n
It is not specifically defined under IPC that what constitute an outrage to women modesty. However, the court has interpreted it in various cases. According to the Supreme Court, modesty is an attribute associated with female human being as a class. Modesty is said to be outraged by such an act of offender which shocks and recognize as an female decency and dignity.\n\n
For example, slapping a women on her butt, asking her for sexual favour, disrobing her etc.\n\n
Essential ingredient of Section 354\n\n
The following are the essential of the offence under Section 354, IPC-\n\n
1. The person who has been a victim of assault must be a woman.\n\n
2. The accused must have used criminal force on her.\n\n
3. An intention to outrage the modesty of a women must be there.</string>
    <string name="sexual_law">Sexual harassment (Section 354A)</string>
    <string name="sex">According to (Section 354A IPC), Sexual harassment is the:\n\n
1. Unwelcome touching or other physical contact\n\n
2. Asking or demanding sex or any other sexual activity\n\n
3. Showing pornographic material which may include videos, magazines, books etc.\n\n
4. Making remarks which are of a sexual nature.\n\n
There is a separate law on sexual harassment at workplaces - The Sexual Harassment at workplaces (prevention, prohibition and redressal) Act and Rulles 2013. There are provisions in the main criminal law (the Indian Penal Code or IPC) which are different from the special law on sexual harassment:\n\n
1. The IPC is not limited to sexual harassment at the workplace, but punishes such harassment done anywhere.\n\n
2. The IPC makes it possible to file a criminal complaint if  you have been sexually harassed, while the special law gives you the option of seeking civil remedies and damages, involving your office administration.\n\n
The punishment for the first three kinds of sexual harassment is three years as compared to the fourth type (making sexually coloured remarks) which is one year.</string>
    <string name="assaults">Assault on women with intent to dirobe a woman (Section 354B)</string>
    <string name="assault_law">Section 354B penalises the offence of assaulting or using  criminal force to a women or abettting any such act with an intention to disrobe or compel her to be naked, with a punishment of not less than three years which a fine. It is a gender specific offence i.e. only a man can be punished under this section.\n\n
Ingredients\n\n
1. The accused must be man.\n\n
2. Use of criminal force or assault or abetment of any such act must be there.\n\n
3. There must be an intention to disrobe a woman or compel her to be naked.</string>
    <string name="voyeurism_law">Voyeurism (Section 354C)</string>
    <string name="voyeurism_laws">This offence came into existence after Nirbhaya Rape Case, 2012 it is mentioned under Section 354C, IPC. The word  "Voyeurism" means appeasement derieved from observing the genital or sexual acts of other usually secretely. This provisione is divided in two different parts. Firstly, when a person watches or captures image of a women engaging in some private act and secondly, when the person disseminate or spread such image.\n\n
The first offence of punishable with imprisonment of not less than one year which may extend  upto three years with fine. The second offence is punishable with imprisonment of not less that three years which may extend upto three years with fine.\n\n
Ingredients\n\n
1. The accused must be a male.\n\n
2. He must watch or capture the image.\n\n
3. The women whose images are captured must be engaged in some private act.\n\n
4. The circumstances must be such that she has the expectations of not being, observed by the perpetrator, or\n\n
5. The accused disseminates that image.</string>
    <string name="stalking_law">Stalking (Section 354D)</string>
    <string name="stalking_laws">Section 354D, IPC talks about the term "stalking" which generally means the act of a following or trying to contact despite disinterest of women. This Section contains two offence. Firstly, where a man follows or contacts or attempts to contact a woman repeatedly despite her clear indication of disinterest and secondly, where a man monitors the use by a woman of the internet, email, or any other form of electronic communication.\n\n
For the first conviction, the punishment prescribed is imprisonment for a term which may extend to three years with fine. The punishment for second conviction may extend upto five years for imprisonment with fine.\n\n
Ingredients:\n\n
1. The accused must be a man and victim must be a woman.\n\n
2. Follo or contact a woman or attempt to contact; or\n\n
3. Monitors the use by the woman of the internet, email or any other electronic communication.\n\n
What does not amount stalking?\n\n
Section 354D has a proviso attached to it which carves out and exception to this offence. If a part of responsibility is imposed on a person by the state to prevent and detect any crime and such acts must be pursued by any law and in the particular circumstances such conduct of the person must be reasonable and justified then, it will not amount to stalking</string>
    <string name="word_law">Word, gesture or act intended to insult the modesty of a woman (Section 509)</string>
    <string name="word_laws">An act which is done intending to insult the modesty of women which may not neccessarily involve any physical force is brought under the shade of this provision through Section 509. This Section intends to determine any kind of aggression into a woman modesty whether by any word, gesture or act or by interuding upon the privacy of such woman this Section is also referred as the "Eve Teasing Section".\n\n
Any person who commits an offence under Section 509 shall be punished with simple improsonment for a term which may extend to three years with fine.\n\n
Essential Ingredients\n\n
This Section require-\n\n
1. An intention to insult the modesty of a woman;\n\n
2. The insult must be caused either by introding upon the privacy of the woman; or by making any gesture or sound. Ottering any word or exhibiting any object. </string>


    <string name="help">Please follow the below steps to setup your account:\n\n\n\t1:Register Your Phone Number.\n\t2:Register Your Guardian Numbers.\n\t3:Always maintain working internet connection.\n\t4:SHAKE your phone in case of emergency to alert your guardians.\n\t\n\n\n\n\tLETS START NOW!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_my_you_tube_location_app">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>


</resources>